producerloops.com 2014-05-03

# Privacy Policy and Legal Statement - Producer Loops

|  | 

|   
---  
  
**PRIVACY POLICY**

ProducerLoops is committed to protecting your privacy online. Our policy explains how we will do this.

**What information do we collect?**

  * We collect email addresses for internal use only. We also give you an option to join our email newsletters when you make a purchase. You can unsubscribe at any time.   

  *  
  * _Registration:_ on some parts of the sites we may ask you to register, and if you do we ask for your name, email address, geographical address and other personal information. 
  *  
  * From time to time we will ask you for further information, for example if you make a purchase or enter a competition. 
  *  
  * We use cookies. For an explanation, see the section on cookies below. 

**Use of Cookies**

Cookies are small files which many web sites transfer to your hard disk. They can inform the web site what pages you visit, and your preferences, which enable web sites to provide you with a more personalized service. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, or to warn you before accepting them.

We use cookies, but most parts of our site can be accessed even if your cookies are turned off. But you may find there are parts of the site which you cannot access if your cookies are turned off.

**Adwords Remarketing**

A small Google Adwords Remarketing cookie is installed when you browse our site. AdWords Remarketing is a Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting service provided by Google. It connects the activity of [www.example.com](http://www.example.com/) with the Adwords advertising network and the Doubleclick Cookie. You can opt out of the cookie tracking here: <http://google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en>

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. Place of processing: USA. - Read the Google [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) to find out more.  

**How do we use your information?**

We use the information to help us understand more about how our web site is used, to improve our site, and to send you information about us and our products which we think may be of interest to you, either electronically or otherwise.

**When do we share information?**

We do not sell your personal information to other companies or individuals.

Some of our product data (the information you see) is managed by third parties, but they do not have access to your personal information or email address.   

If we believe that your use of the site is unlawful or damaging to others, we reserve the right to disclose the information we have obtained through the site about you to the extent that it is reasonably necessary in our opinion to prevent, remedy or take action in relation to such conduct.  

Download 300MB of Samples, Loops & Reason Refills for FREE when you sign up to our Weekly Newsletter:

0800 098 8607
